<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2017 Tcl Corporation Limited -->
<!-- Copyright (C) 2016 Tcl Corporation Limited -->
<resources xmlns:xliff="http://schemas.android.com/tools" xmlns:tools="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <!--title and content of PP-->
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <!--title and content of TC-->
    <!--Defect:2677605 junping.zhang 20160905 changed-->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use">Terms and conditions of use</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_one">These Terms and Conditions of use tell you how you may use the User Center application and online service (“Service”) to access.\nThis Service is published by TCL Communication Ltd. hereinafter referred to as “ALCATEL”, registered at Room 19 12 A, Tower 3, China Hong Kong City, 33 Canton Road, Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon, Hong-Kong.\nPlease read through these Terms and Conditions of Use and our Privacy Policy  (hereinafter “Terms and Conditions”) carefully. These Terms and Conditions are a contract between you and TCL Communication Ltd. and may be amended from time to time. If you don’t agree to the Terms and Conditions, do not use the Service. If you do use the Service, you accept and agree to these Terms and Conditions.\nThe purpose and some content of this Service may not be adapted for minors. By accessing this Website, you guarantee that you are not a minor and are entitled by the law of your country of domicile to access the Website.\n\n<b>Guidelines of Use</b>\n\nWhen you create an ONETOUCH account or register e-warranty, we will ask you to provide us with some personal information, such as your email address, nickname, location and your profile photo. Your personal information will be collected, stored and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy and in compliance with the governing law, which you shall read before using this Service.\nYour email address will be your ONETOUCH user name, which you will use to log-into your account. We do not display your email address to other users of the Service.\nYou may also log in with a 3rd party account. In case you login with a 3rd party account such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+, we will use the registered email in those 3rd party as your user name. Please note that if you register with your 3rd party account, respectively their terms and conditions and their privacy policy will apply respectively.\nBy registering you will also benefit from the a range of Services that we will offer you, and notably after sales services, hotline, e warranty and you can get in touch with us any time you wish.\nFor the after sales services, you will find all necessary addresses worldwide of our repair centers.\nFor hot line, there is list of phone numbers that you can dial for an efficient and immediate support and consumer experience.\nIf you want to store your data of your smartphone, such as contacts, photos, call logs, SMS within the 2G free storage space, and access it with other devices, such as your PC or tablets, you should create an ONETOUCH account.\nBy registering into the Service, you will have direct access to your phone information, IMEI, the model and the activation date, which will automatically benefit you.\nOur goal is to help you store and access your own data freely.\n\n<b>Intellectual Property</b>\n\nExcept for the user generated content if any, the Service, including all copyrights, trademarks, and other intellectual property rights therein are protected by intellectual property rights and are owned by ALCATEL or a third party.\nYou may not reproduce, distribute, modify or create derivative works of, publicly display (including by framing any content), or commercially exploit any part of the Service except as necessary to view the content therein and to create a reasonable number of copies of portions of such content (without modification) for your personal, non-commercial use.\nIf you believe that any content of the application violates any third party intellectual property rights, please contact us immediately. We, as soon as we receive your notification, will take necessary action to cease any such violation and remove any illicit content.\nALCATEL trademark, the logo and any other trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos used in connection with this Website are trademarks or registered trademarks of ALCATEL or its licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos used in connection with the Website may be the trademarks of t
heir respective owners. You are granted no right or license with respect to any of the aforesaid trademarks and any use of such trademarks.\nIn the event of any violations of the above, ALCATEL reserves the right to ask you to immediately stop or rectify the unlawful use, or, should the unlawful use and/or violation continue, ALCATEL reserves the right to file a claim against you.\n\n</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_two"><b>Data Protection and Privacy</b>\n\nAny information which you provide to us from which ALCATEL can identify you are held and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy.\nIn connection with your use of the Service, you may share with us your email address for further communication between you and ALCATEL. Prior to giving out your email address, please review our Privacy Policy in order to understand how we collect and use information about you when you access, visit or use the Website.\nYour personal information will be collected, stored and processed in accordance with our Privacy Policy and the applicable law. \n\n<b>Warranty disclaimer; limitation of liabilities</b>\n\nThe Service is provided by ALCATEL "as is."\nTo the full extent permissible by applicable law, neither ALCATEL nor its partners, suppliers, or affiliates make any representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the Service, its contents, or any information made available by or through the Service. In addition, ALCATEL and its partners disclaim all warranties with respect to the Service, express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, title, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. Furthermore, ALCATEL does not warrant that use of the Service will be uninterrupted, available at any time or from any particular location, secure or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Service is free of viruses or other potentially harmful components. You shall be responsible for backing up your own system.\nALCATEL does not make any other promises or warranties about the Service and in particular does not warrant and shall not be liable for any claim that results from a decision made by ALCATEL to remove or refuse to process any information or content, to warn you, to suspend or terminate your access to the Service, or to take any other action during the investigation of a suspected violation or as a result of ALCATEL conclusion that a violation of these Terms and Conditions has occurred; or it relates to loss of income, business or profits, or any loss of data or corruption of data in connection with your use of the Application or the Service.\nIn no event will ALCATEL accept liability for any description, including liability for negligence (except for personal injury or death), for any damages or losses whatsoever (including, without limitation, loss of business, revenue, profits, or consequential loss) resulting from the use of or your inability to use the Service.\nIf you breach these Terms and Conditions, you will be liable to ALCATEL, its directors, officers, employees, affiliates, agents, contractors, and licensors for any claim arising out of your breach. You will also be liable for any action taken by ALCATEL as part of its investigation of a suspected violation of these Terms and Conditions, or as a result of its findings or decision that a violation of these Terms and Conditions has occurred.\n\n</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_of_use_content_three"><b>Links to third-party sites</b>\n\nThe Service may also contain links to websites, which are not under the control of or maintained by ALCATEL. ALCATEL is not responsible for the content of those websites. ALCATEL provides these links for your convenience only and does not necessarily endorse the material on these sites.\nThe use by you of these third party websites creates a direct relationship between you and such third parties. It is therefore your responsibility to read and comply with such third parties privacy policies and their terms and conditions, which apply to their websites. All and any claims with regards to such third party websites or content found on websites shall be directed to such third parties. \n\n<b>Changes</b>\n\nALCATEL reserves the right to modify these Terms and Conditions at any time. Such modifications and additional terms and conditions will be communicated to you and, if accepted, they will be effective immediately and will be incorporated into these Terms and Conditions. In the event that you refuse to accept such changes, you shall cease to access the Service and the Application immediately. Should you continue to use the Service despite your disagreement to the Terms and Conditions or to any changes thereof, ALCATEL shall not be liable for any claims resulting thereof.\n\n<b>Governing law. Jurisdiction</b>\n\nThis Service is controlled and operated by ALCATEL offices based in PR China. By accessing this Service, you agree that the laws of PR China will apply to the matters relating to the use of this Service, without regard to principles of the conflicts of laws.\nIn the event of a dispute, disagreement between ALCATEL and you arising out of or in connection with your use of the Service, the parties shall attempt, promptly and in good faith, to resolve any such dispute. If we are unable to resolve any such dispute within a reasonable time (not to exceed thirty (30) days), then either party may submit such controversy or dispute to the competent courts of PR China.\n\n<b>Miscellaneous</b>\n\nIf any of the provisions of these Terms and Conditions are held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be void or unenforceable, such provisions shall be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary and replaced with a valid provision that best embodies the intent of these Terms and Conditions, so that these shall remain in full force and effect.\nThese Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and ALCATEL with regard to your use of the Service, and any and all other written or oral agreements or understandings previously existing between you and ALCATEL with respect to such use are hereby superseded and cancelled.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="and">&#160;and&#160;</string>
    <string name="more_info">For more information,please read our&#160;</string>
</resources>
